A Guide to the San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Records, 1931-2008 (bulk 1985-2005)
San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Records
- Audiovisual and Digital Materials
  - Beta Cam (Box 34)
    - San Antonio Chamber of Commerce: technology, Medical, Industrial in English and Spanish (SP S), January 10, 2002 (Box AV9)
    - El Corazon de San Antonio (SP S), January 28, 2004 (Box AV9)
    - El Corazon de San Antonio Title Loop (SP L), January 27, 2004 (Box AV9)
  - CD (Box AV2)
    - Pictures Leadership San Antonio (LSA) XXIX, 2003-2004 (Box AV2)
    - 2004 Valero Texas Open: Bienvenidos Luncheon, 2004 (Box AV2)
    - Leadership San Antonio (LSA) Closing Retreat, 2003-2004 (Box AV2)
    - Leadership San Antonio (LSA) XXIX, 2003 (Box AV2)
    - Bilingual Yellow Pages, undated (Box AV2)
    - Communication Folder Archives, 2000-2003 (Box AV2)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Staff Unedited, undated (Box AV2)
    - Leadership San Antonio (LSA) XXIX, 2003-2004 (Box AV2)
    - Think Big, Buy Small, undated (Box AV2)
    - Alexander E. Briseeadership Development Program Grad class of 2004, 2004 (Box AV2)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce: 2006 Membership Directory, 2006 (Box AV2)
  - DVD (Box AV2)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, May 8, 2006 (Box AV2)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce: Inside S.A.- July Event Calendar, June 27, 2006 (Box AV2)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce: Inside S.A. Calendar, September 22, 2006 (Box AV2)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce: Inside S.A., undated (Box AV2)
    - Network Reel, January 24, 2005 (Box AV2)
    - Lincoln Mark LT "revised" Music, January 24, 2005 (Box AV2)
    - Hispanic Chamber Golf Tournament, undated (Box AV2)
  - Zip Disk (Box AV2)
    - MX Chamber, undated (Box AV2)
    - 73rd Installation Banquet Program Images, undated (Box AV2)
    - Main Newsletter Images, undated (Box AV2)
    - January-April 2003 Newsletter and 2004 75th Anniversary Celebration, 2003-2004 (Box AV2)
    - The Hispanic Chamber Logos Ad Campaign, undated (Box AV2)
    - May-June 2002 Newsletter, 2002 (Box AV2)
    - 73rd Installation Banquet Program Images, undated (Box AV2)
  - Digital Data Storage (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (DDS-1), 1998-1999 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (DDS-1), January 8, 1999 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (DDS-1), May 3, 1999 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (DDS-1), December 30, 1998 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (DDS-1), 1998-1999 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (DDS-1), undated (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (Travan 20), July 27, 2005 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (Travan 20), 2004-2005 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (Travan 20), 2005 (Box AV2)
    - Hispanic Chamber (DV Cam), undated (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (Compact video Cassette), undated (Box AV2)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce (Mini Data Cartridge), 1997 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (Mini Data Cartridge), August 28, 1997 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (Mini Data Cartridge), 1997 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (Mini Data Cartridge), 1997-1998 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (Mini Data Cartridge), 1997-1998 (Box AV2)
    - Untitled (Mini Data Cartridge), January 12, 1998 (Box AV3)
    - Untitled (Mini Data Cartridge), undated (Box AV3)
  - 3.5 inch Floppy Disk (Box AV7)
    - Untitled, November 30, 1994 (Box AV7)
    - Leadership San Antonio (LSA), Members, Mixers, September 3, 1996 (Box AV7)
    - Intern, September 3, 1996 (Box AV7)
    - 1994 Plan, September 3, 1996 (Box AV7)
    - Business Development, Golf, Government, September 3, 1996 (Box AV7)
    - PR, Illegible, September 3, 1996 (Box AV7)
    - Corporate, September 3, 1996 (Box AV7)
    - 1996 Banquets, September 3, 1996 (Box AV7)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Newsletters, Reports, TAMACC, 1996-1997 (Box AV7)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce April 1997 Newsletter, Apr-97 (Box AV7)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 97.TXT, July 17, 1997 (Box AV7)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 97.TXT, October 6, 1997 (Box AV7)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, November 7, 1997 (Box AV7)
    - Company Bonus, Budget Plan, 1997 (Box AV7)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Schedule, 1997 (Box AV7)
    - Audit Schedules, 1997 (Box AV7)
    - Audit Schedules Back Up, 1998 (Box AV7)
    - 1998 Budget, 1998 (Box AV7)
    - Audit Report, Members, Cash Budget, 1998-1999 (Box AV7)
    - Hispanic Chamber Gala A.D., Jan-99, [ 2 Disks ] (Box AV7)
    - Budget, 1999 (Box AV7)
    - Anthony Baeck Contacts, January 5, 2001 (Box AV7)
    - Files, undated (Box AV7)
    - John Gary Herrera's Files, undated (Box AV7)
    - FTA Logos, undated (Box AV7)
    - Roseanne Career Services, undated (Box AV7)
    - Simple IRA Transmittal Form, undated (Box AV7)
    - Conversion Program, undated (Box AV7)
    - Employee List, undated (Box AV7)
    - African American Data, undated (Box AV7)
    - Quark, undated, [ 4 Disks ] (Box AV7)
    - CPS Database Backup, undated (Box AV7)
    - Database Backup, undated (Box AV7)
    - Check Request 1 and 2, Journal Mileage, Pay DED, Payroll Change, Receivable, undated (Box AV7)
    - Members and Other Representatives and Member Representative Sample, undated (Box AV7)
    - Audit- Client Representative Letter, undated (Box AV7)
    - United States Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box AV7)
    - EFI Color (Box AV7)
    - Baptist Child and family Services, undated (Box AV7)
    - S.A.M. Tutor, undated (Box AV7)
    - BCFS, undated, [ Disks 1-3, 6 ] (Box AV7)
    - Untitled, undated, [ 36 Disks ] (Box AV7)
  - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce “Pride” (Kids), April 9, 1993, [reel to reel] (Box 34)
- Artifacts
  - Texas Association of Mexican-American Chambers of Commerce Certificate of Membership, 2005 (Box 50)
  - Hispanic Contractors Association Membership, undated (Box 50)
  - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Blank Plaque, undated (Box 50)
  - Appreciation Plaque for John Langoria, July 1, 1999 (Box 50)
  - 1995 Corporate Partner Plaque, 1995 (Box 50)
  - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Plaque, March 2005 (Box 50)
  - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Bronze Sponsor Plaque, 2003-2004 (Box 50)
  - Texas Association of Business Member Plaque, undated (Box 50)
  - Fiesta Buttons, 2000-2006 (Box 50)
  - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Pins, undated (Box 50)
  - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Member Plaque, undated (Box 51)
  - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Plaque, undated (Box 51)
  - General Motors Support Plaque, October 13, 2005 (Box 51)
  - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Tablecloth, undated (Box 51)
- Addition of March 2007 (Accession 2007-036 and Accession 2007-058 ), Addition of May 2007 (Accession 2007-058) has been merged with the Addition of March 2007 and includes 2 Fiesta medals, a member bio for Max Navarro, and a 2007 program.
  The bulk of the material in the Addition of March 2007 is Board of Directors and Executive Committee meeting minutes and correspondence. Also included are assorted administrative records and awards and plaques.
  - Board correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 2007/1, Folder 1)
  - Pan American Games correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 2007/ 1, Folder 1-3)
  - 2007 Pan American bid games, 2001 (Box 2007/1, Folder 4)
  - Internal correspondence, 2006 (Box 2007/1, Folder 5-6)
  - Board correspondence, 1995 (Box 2007/1, Folder 7)
  - Board minutes, 1995 (Box 2007/1, Folder 8-9)
  - San Antonio Sports Foundation correspondence, 2000 (Box 2007/1, Folder 10)
  - Executive committee meetings, 2000 (Box 2007/1, Folder 11-12)
  - Minutes, June-December 1996 (Box 2007/1, Folder 13-14)
  - Board of Directors meetings,2000 (Box 2007/1, Folder 1-3)
  - Board of Directors and Executive committee meetings, 1987 (Box 2007/2, Folder 5)
  - Hispanic Resource Guide, 1994 (Box 2007/2, Folder 6-9)
  - Executive and Board meetings, memos, etc., 1995 (Box 2007/2, Folder 10-11)
  - Board of Directors and Executive committee meetings, 1997 (Box 2007/2, Folder 12-14)
  - Board correspondence, 1997 (Box 2007/2, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors and Executive Committee meetings, 2000 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors and Executive Committee meetings, 1998 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors and Executive Committee meetings, 1997 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rico Trade Mission, August 16-18, 2000 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 4)
  - Trade Mission to San Luis Potosi/Aguascalientes, September 6-9, 2000 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 5)
  - San Antonio to DC XXII trip, September 24-26, 2000 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 6)
  - South America Trade Mission to Chile and Argentina, October21-29, 2000 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 7)
  - Executive committee, Board of Directors, 2006 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 8)
  - Assorted administrative documents, 2006 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 9)
  - Chihuahua Delegation reception and visit to San Antonio, February 9, 2000 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 10)
  - Canary Islands, Spain delegation, visit to San Antonio, June 18-23, 2000 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee and Board of Directors meetings, 1998 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 12-13)
  - Board of Directors and Executive Committee meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors and Executive Committee meetings, 1998 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 15)
  - External correspondence, 1997 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 16-17)
  - Board correspondence, 1997 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 18)
  - Executive committee minutes, 1996 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 19)
  - Board correspondence, 1996 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 20)
  - BRAC Strategy Retreat, August 22, 1994 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 21)
  - Annual report, 2006 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 22)
  - Fiesta pins, 2007 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 23)
  - Executive Committee meetings, 1999 (Box 2007/ 3, Folder 24-26)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1999 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 1)
  - Executive and Board of Directors minutes, 1995 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 2-4)
  - Board of Directors and Executive committee, 1995-1996 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 5-7)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 8)
  - Internal correspondence, 1994 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors, 1993-1994 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 11-12)
  - Executive Board meeting, 1994 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 13-14)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 16)
  - External correspondence, 1994 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors, 1993 (Box 2007/ 4, Folder 18-19)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1987 (Box 2007/ 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Certificate of Appreciation-Tejano Heritage month, 2006 (Box 2007/ 5, Folder 4)
  - Appreciation award from Texas Association of Mexican-American Chambers of Commerce, 6th Annual convention host, July 31, 1981 (Box 2007/ 5, Folder 5)
  - Certificates and recognitions, 1984, 1997 and undated (Box 2007/ 5, Folder 6)
  - Department of the Navy- Toys for Tots certificate, November 28, 2000 (Box 2007/ 5, Folder 7)
  - Awards and plaques, 1979-1984, 1990-2003 and undated (Box 2007/ 5, Folder 8)
  - Awards, plaques, proclamations, 1979-2004 (Box 2007/ OM1)
- Addition of March 2008 (Accession 2008-015)
  Includes material related to special events, banquets, awards, budgets and other administrative material, membership directories, CDs, DVDs, and photos.
  - Special events budgets, 2004 (Box 2008-015/1, Folder 1)
  - Business Networking Mixers, 2004 (Box 2008-015/1, Folder 2-4)
  - Business Awards, 2004-2005 (Box 2008-015/1, Folder 5-6)
  - Busines Awards Banquet, 2004 (Box 2008-015/1, Folder 7-9)
  - Business Awards, 2003 (Box 2008-015/1, Folder 10-13)
  - Special events budgets, 2003 (Box 2008-015/1, Folder 14)
  - Hispanic Chamber Receptions, 2003 (Box 2008-015/1, Folder 15-17)
  - River Parade Pachanga, 2003-2004 (Box 2008-015/2, Folder 1-2)
  - Business Awards banquet, 2003 (Box 2008-015/2, Folder 3-5)
  - Website advertising, 2003-2004 (Box 2008-015/2, Folder 6)
  - Membership directory, 1996 (Box 2008-015/2, Folder 7-8)
  - River Parade Pachanga, 2002 (Box 2008-015/2, Folder 9)
  - Membership directory, 2001 (Box 2008-015/2, Folder 10)
  - Directory, 2001 (Box 2008-015/2, Folder 11-12)
  - Leadership San Antonio (LSA), 2000-2001 (Box 2008-015/2, Folder 13-14)
  - 74th Annual Installation banquet (2 of 2), January 23, 2003 (Box 2008-015/3, Folder 1-3)
  - 74th Annual Installation banquet (1 of 2), January 23, 2003 (Box 2008-015/3, Folder 4-6)
  - 73rd Annual Installation banquet, January 16, 2002 (Box 2008-015/3, Folder 7-9)
  - 72nd Annual Installation banquet, January 16, 2001 (Box 2008-015/3, Folder 10-13)
  - 71st Annual Installation banquet, January 11, 2000 (Box 2008-015/3, Folder 14)
  - 71st Annual Installation banquet, January 11, 2000 (Box 2008-015/4, Folder 1-3)
  - Newsletter Advertising, 1996-1998 (Box 2008-015/4, Folder 4)
  - Resolutions, 1996-1997 (Box 2008-015/4, Folder 5)
  - Special events budgets, 2004-2005 (Box 2008-015/4, Folder 6)
  - Hispanic Chamber Business Awards Banquet, 2005 (Box 2008-015/4, Folder 7-8)
  - Hispanic Chamber Business Awards, 2005 (Box 2008-015/4, Folder 9-11)
  - booklet Code Red, The Critical Condition of Health in Texas, the Summary, undated (Box 2008-015/4, Folder 12)
  - Imagine…Imaginate…San Antonio, If you could conduct business in English and Spanish, 1999 (Box 2008-015/4, Folder 13)
  - Imaginate…Imagine…If you could say it in English and Spanish, 1999 (Box 2008-015/4, Folder 14)
  - Assorted cards, invitations and event announcements, 2007-2008 and undated (Box 2008-015/5, Folder 15)
  - Annual reports, 2006-2007 (Box 2008-015/5, Folder 16)
  - Business Awards banquet programs, 2007 (Box 2008-015/5, Folder 17)
  - CDs and DVD: membership directories, Archives, Everything:video:audio, 2002-2008 (Box 2008-015/5, Folder 18)
  - Healthcare summit, 2007 (Box 2008-015/5, Folder 19)
  - Ephemera, undated (Box 2008-015/5, Folder 20)
  - Chairman of the Board plaques, 1963-1999 (Box 2008-015/ 6)
  - Photos, 1998-1999 and undated (Box 2008-015OM1)
- Addition of December 2008 (Acc. 2008-075)1992-2008
  Includes meeting minutes, material documenting events and award programs, membership directories, meeting notes, reports, DVD’s, awards, and a plaque from businesses and initiatives related to the San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce.
  - Executive Committee and Board of Directors minutes,2003-2004 (Box 2008-075/1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee and Board of Directors minutes,2002 (Box 2008-075/1, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes,2004 (Box 2008-075/1, Folder 3-6)
  - Board of Directors meetings,2001 (Box 2008-075/1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors,2004 (Box 2008-075/1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee meetings, 2004 (Box 2008-075/1, Folder 9-11)
  - Board of Directors meeting,2003 (Box 2008-075/1, Folder 12-13)
  - Executive Committee meeting,2003 (Box 2008-075/1, Folder 14-15)
  - Board of Directors meetings,2002 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 1-3)
  - Executive Committee meetings,2002 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 4-5)
  - Board of Directors meetings,2001 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 6-8)
  - Board of Directors Nominations Committee,2001 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 9)
  - TAMACC 25th Annual Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27-29, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 10)
  - TAMACC-budget documentation, Golf Club of Texas, San Antonio, TX, 25th Anniversary Convention and Business Expo,July 27, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 11)
  - TAMACC 25th Annual Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27-29, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 12)
  - TAMACC-faxes sent regarding 25th Anniversary Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27-29, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 13)
  - TAMACC-golf tournament documentation, Golf Club of Texas, 25th Anniversary Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 14)
  - TAMACC-media documentation, 25th Anniversary Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27-29, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 15)
  - TAMACC-past events documentation, 25th Anniversary Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27-29, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 16)
  - TAMACC-meeting notes, 25th Anniversary Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27-29, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 17)
  - TAMACC-schedule information, 25th Anniversary Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27-29, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 18)
  - TAMACC-signed contracts, 25th Anniversary Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27-29, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 19)
  - TAMACC-sponsorship documentation, 25th Anniversary Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27-29, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 20-21)
  - TAMACC-workshop and convention documentation, 25th Anniversary Convention and Business Expo, San Antonio, Texas,July 27-29, 2000 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 22)
  - 4th annual Dieciseis de Septiembre Noche Mexicana Gala, Hyatt Regency Hotel,September 11, 1999 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 23)
  - Business Achievement awards, Plaza San Antonio Hotel,October 8, 1999 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 24)
  - Brillante Awards, National Society Hispanic MBA's,1999 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 25)
  - Corporate Investors Breakfast, Doubletree Hotel, 7:30 a.m., December 1, 1999 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 26)
  - Consul's Annual Address US-Mexico Relations 1999-The Year in Review, Westin Riverwalk San Antonio,December 2, 1999 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 27)
  - TAMACC-05,2007 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 28)
  - Executive team meeting,2007 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 29)
  - Alliance of Chambers Correspondence,2002-2004 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 30)
  - Copies of reciepts,2003 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 31)
  - USHCC 26th Annual National Convention and Business Expo,2005 (Box 2008-075/2, Folder 32)
  - Institute recap,1997 (Box 2008-075/2, Folders 33)
  - Chamber accomplishments,2002 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 1)
  - Texas Biological and Agro-Defence Consortium, undated (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 2)
  - Summaries, plannings and organizational charts, undated (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 3)
  - A Guide to Starting Your Business in San Antonio,1998 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 4)
  - Bank of America Foundation, Neighborhood Excellence Initiative, Local Market Selection Committee meeting notebook, undated (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 5)
  - Certificates,1992-2000 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 6)
  - San Antonio, Texas, Center for Trade in the Americas,2004 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 7)
  - Central Catholic High School, annual report,July 2003-2004 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 8)
  - Alameda correspondence,June 30, 2005 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 9)
  - San Antonio Lighthouse, William Judson Center, Creating Opportunities for Individual Independence,2004 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 10)
  - Masters Leadership Program of San Antonio and Bexar County,2004-2005 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 11)
  - Voices for Children of San Antonio, 6th annual Congress on Children,September 22, 2004 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 12)
  - The Cultural Collaborative: A Community Plan for San Antonio's Creative Economy,2004 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 13)
  - American Red Cross, undated (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 14)
  - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, membership directory,2004-2005 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 15)
  - Kelly USA, undated (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 16)
  - Smart Start, undated (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 17)
  - Hispanic Association of Colleges and Universities,2004 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 18)
  - 25th Annual National Convention and Business Expo, Celebrating Hispanic Enterprise,2004 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 19)
  - San Antonio Symphony,2004-2005 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 20)
  - Viva el Mariachi! Mariachi Vargas de Tecalitlan,2002 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 21)
  - The Social and Health Research Center, The Bienestar/Neema Health Program,2004 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 22)
  - Weekly staff meetings and reports,2005 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 23-25)
  - Bexar Presidents Institute,2004 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 26)
  - The Texas Institute for School Boards, Santa Fe, New MexicoJune 27-30, 2003 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 27-28)
  - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce personal membership contacts, undated (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 29)
  - SATAI executive search,July 27, 2005 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 30)
  - Calendar emails,2005-2006 (Box 2008-075/3, Folder 31)
  - Strategic planning notes,2005-2006 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 1)
  - Staff strategic report,2005 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors,2002 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors,2005 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 4)
  - Staff strategic action plan,2004-2005 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 5)
  - Staff strategic planning retreat,December 1-2, 2005 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors strategic retreat,November 21, 2005 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 7)
  - Board retreat,September 9-10, 2004 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 8)
  - Events worksheets-Reyes, undated (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors, current month meeting documentation,2006 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 10)
  - Files,2001 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 11-12)
  - The Cultural Collaborative, undated (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 13)
  - Center for Trade in the Americas, San Antonio to Mexico City Trade Mission, (AJ's notes)October 18-20, 2005 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 14)
  - Omega Health Group, undated (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 15)
  - Texas sales and use tax exemption certification forms, undated (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 16)
  - Phone conference,2004 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 17)
  - Fundraising campaign,2002 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 18)
  - SATAI,2004 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 19)
  - Executive committee meeting notes,2001 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors meeting notes,2001 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 21)
  - Joint task force, Greater San Antonio and Hispanic Chambers of Commerce,2001 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 22)
  - Events worksheet, (AJ),2006 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors,2004 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 24)
  - DVD's,2008 and undated (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 25)
  - Business Awards Banquet programs and postcards,2008 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 26)
  - Postcards and flyers for events,2007-2008 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 27)
  - The Quarterly newsletter,2008 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 28)
  - Membership information,2008 (Box 2008-075/4, Folder 29)
  - Name tags, undated (Box 2008-075/4)
  - Awards,1998-2001 (Box 2008-075/4)
  - Plaque from Hispanic Business Top 500 Reception,October 13, 2005 (Box 2008-075/OM1)